<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on From Another Planet: Mind-space-junks</title>
    <link>https://mrvkrt.github.io/anotherplanet/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on From Another Planet: Mind-space-junks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mrvkrt.github.io/anotherplanet/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beyond a Horror Game – Martha is Dead</title>
      <link>https://mrvkrt.github.io/anotherplanet/post/martha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrvkrt.github.io/anotherplanet/post/martha/</guid>
      <description>Martha Is Dead is a horror game released on February 24, 2022. But beyond being a horror game, it&amp;rsquo;s more of a psychological experience. It deals with personal and so complex topics that it is obvious that some players may find it triggering.
Even it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;perfect experience for me&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m sure most players consider it’s just a walking simulation. (Not that I care…)
The game starts with a folk tale, takes place in 1944 in Italy, during the World War II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting of the Band-wagon</title>
      <link>https://mrvkrt.github.io/anotherplanet/post/pop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrvkrt.github.io/anotherplanet/post/pop/</guid>
      <description>“The bandwagon effect is the term used to describe the tendency for people to adopt certain behaviors, styles, or attitudes simply because others are doing so.” …
Yes, yes, as a &amp;ldquo;boomer&amp;rdquo; now maybe I&amp;rsquo;m whining as usual. Even so, since you don&amp;rsquo;t have to read this, I can keep whining, right? Although I am actually very old, I think my soul ages before actual, physical me. Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s why I suddenly lose my enthusiasm when I see something that I&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for so much being watched, read or expressed by “popular culture” or should I say “bandwagon”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Smell of Success</title>
      <link>https://mrvkrt.github.io/anotherplanet/post/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrvkrt.github.io/anotherplanet/post/success/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Smell of Success is a 1957 American film noir drama film directed by Alexander Mackendrick, starring Burt Lancaster, Tony Curtis, Susan Harrison which is one of my favorite noir films. But I’m not going to talk about this movie. While I was listening to movie’s soundtrack suddenly found myself to questioning what success really is and I wanted to clear my thoughts. …
Generally, people think success connected with status and financial terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loop of Choices</title>
      <link>https://mrvkrt.github.io/anotherplanet/post/stanley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mrvkrt.github.io/anotherplanet/post/stanley/</guid>
      <description>“As a white-collar employee Stanley, only presses the buttons after commands he receives. One day he worried because he hasn&amp;rsquo;t received any commands and then realized his co-workers are gone. But no worries, a narrator appears to help him(?)” …
Narrator tells Stanley exactly what to do. But how reliable is this narrator? Does Stanley need help? Or does he not have free will of his own? Doesn&amp;rsquo;t he make a choice in the end, whether it fits the narrators say or not?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
