<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on From Another Planet: Mind-space-junks</title>
    <link>https://anotherplanet.website/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on From Another Planet: Mind-space-junks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anotherplanet.website/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting of the Band-wagon</title>
      <link>https://anotherplanet.website/post/pop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotherplanet.website/post/pop/</guid>
      <description>“The bandwagon effect is the term used to describe the tendency for people to adopt certain behaviors, styles, or attitudes simply because others are doing so.” …
 Yes, yes, as a &amp;ldquo;boomer&amp;rdquo; now maybe I&amp;rsquo;m whining as usual. Even so, since you don&amp;rsquo;t have to read this, I can keep whining, right? Although I am actually very old, I think my soul ages before actual, physical me. Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s why I suddenly lose my enthusiasm when I see something that I&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for so much being watched, read or expressed by “popular culture” or should I say “bandwagon”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Smell of Success</title>
      <link>https://anotherplanet.website/post/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotherplanet.website/post/success/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Smell of Success is a 1957 American film noir drama film directed by Alexander Mackendrick, starring Burt Lancaster, Tony Curtis, Susan Harrison which is one of my favorite noir films. But I’m not going to talk about this movie. While I was listening to movie’s soundtrack suddenly found myself to questioning what success really is and I wanted to clear my thoughts. …
 Generally, people think success connected with status and financial terms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
